another thing that I learned at maralago
this weekend was that uh John Ratcliffe
the new CIA director designate the
three- term uh House member from Texas
is really the guy on intelligence and
National Security issues it's not
Congressman Mike walls The New National
Security adviser it's not tulsy gabard
it's John Ratcliffe and of all of the
people involved in National Security and
I'm including Marco Rubio in
that it is Ratliff who who is the most
neocon he claims to be a magga
republican he claims to be one of these
people who is opposed to foreign
interventions I'm just not sure that
that's true and if he's the one who has
Trump's ear more readily than anybody
else I'm going to be a little bit
worried about that